question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In &quot;The Sims&quot; series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code&quot;, you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In Undertale, having a &quot;Fun Value&quot; set to 56-57 will play the &quot;Wrong Number Song Call&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "TF2: Sentry rocket damage falloff is calculated based on the distance between the sentry and the enemy, not the engineer and the enemy",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "All of these maps were in &quot;Tom Clancy&#039;s Rainbow Six Siege&quot; on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, Border, Consulate.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In The Witcher 3, the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Man&#039;s Tree.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
